Hello everyone, welcome to a new video and it's something special today. It's lingerie
because I received two sets from Paradise and yeah it is something new for me as well.
But first let's talk about these pants. These are the Paradise Aesthetic Thermal Classic Pants
or classic thermal whatever it's the winter version so to say you may have seen the other
two aesthetic pants by paradise in my previous video and this is the thicker thermal version
for winter and i wanted to talk about long-term testing so to say because i've been wearing these
pants for weeks sometimes two three four days a week in the office and wherever I go sometimes
even just to sit at home and I have to say they still look great there are no material strains
there are no issues with the sewing everything is fine so I can tell you that after like wearing
them for multiple times they still do look great they still fit great and I did not have any
problems so far so it's the middle of May here in Germany and still rather cold outside I really
like to wear these ones at the moment compared to the normal aesthetic classic pants because
even though they're thermal version they're not that thick I can show you some close-ups so if
it's not high summertime you can totally wear them in whatever weather. Of course they have the
typical booty cut as well from Paradise with the lines here which really makes a great figure and
I really have to say after wearing it for all these hours it is really like the most comfortable
fake leather pants I own. But actually I wanted to show you the lingerie from
Paradise. They did make the lingerie before they made the pants and I have
this bright orange and this rather toned down black and nude ensemble here.
totally confused already with all the straps. Yeah let's see how this is going
to work and fit. Ta-da! This is I think it's my favorite set of the two probably
because it's black or yeah black and nude and I really think it looks just
beautiful for lingerie. The bra is not padded and I think I'm wearing size medium and it is super
comfy although there are wires here you don't feel them and the pants are kind of comfy as well. I
didn't expect them to be comfortable to be honest because of all the thin straps and stuff but yeah
they're comfortable I think they look really cool the additional decorative
straps here and I have to confess I'm not used to showing so much skin here so
I probably won't turn around although it really looks nice on the backside as
well but to see that you maybe have to check out their homepage because the
best Latouines the owners of the company do make great pictures with the
lingerie as well so you don't need that from me. By the way it is not see-through
here so the nude part is another layer you can't see through which is really
cool. But there is a second set and I don't know what to call the color if
it's coral or salmon or some kind of orange. I wanted to try this because
Because there is one really cool specialty here. This is a push-up bra that is not wired.
So you can like bend, totally bend the cups here. Which makes it even more comfortable.
And there's a front clasp and a really cool back side here. But yeah, I'll change into it.
This is really colourful, especially together with my hair.
And I think it is really the hair that makes me like this colour as well.
Because I think it looks not too bad together.
And I have to say this bra is genius.
I mean it's push up padded and not wire so it's so comfortable.
it still has this push-up effect and I have to say girls this is like a really
great design because you men may not notice but a bra without wires really is
more comfortable most of the time and since women are wearing bras all day it
is important that it is comfortable. But yeah I think I like this overall
combination. Not sure about the panties here. They're rather tight. Yeah, anyway. If you want
to see more of these sets then you should check out my Patreon and consider supporting me there.
I'll link it down below. Other than that I have to say I think I'm done with this video and
yeah I wish you have a nice day. I hope you enjoyed this video. Leave a comment
and tell me if you did. See you around. Bye.